

SHANTELL DASILVA

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER



PERSONAL PROFILE

I have 2 years of experience managing social profiles or other online communities, including analytics, moderation and influencer identification with a proven track record of launching successful multi-channel (social, online, offline events), improving ecommerce sales, online and social network. I also have strong project management, strategic planning and writing skills



LIST OF TOOLS

PLATFORMS

- Wordpress
- Hootsuite
- Google Analytics
- Sprout
- Shopify

SOFTWARE

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Premiere Pro
- Audacity

SOCIAL MEDIA CHANNELS

- Instagram
- YouTube
- Facebook
 - Tic Tok
 - **Pintrest**

CONTACT

INFORMATION

phone: (862) 283-8112

Email: shantelldigitalegmail.com Website: www.Shantelldasilva.com

Address: Jersey City, NJ



WORK HISTORY

Pressed By Shany

Social Media Manager

2020 to Present

- Use data and analytics tools to draw conclusions and make strategic optimizations
- Used Sprout to optimize posts.
- Increased reach by more than 1,000,000% in the first 2 weeks!
- Created creative content and edited videos through video premiere.
- Handled email marketing through mail chimp.

Moss Sauce

Social Media Manager

2020 to Present

- Use data and analytics tools to draw conclusions and make strategic optimizations
- · Used Hootsuite to optimize posts.
- · Increased reach by more than 700%
- Worked with SEO to optimize company.
- · Handled email marketing through mail chimp.

Taste of the Caribbean Festival

Social Media Manager

2021 to Present

- Select social posts being mindful of many different objectives boosting content, driving newsletter enrollments, gaining fans, acquiring subscribers - and carefully determine what mix drives maximum return.
- Increased customer reach and interaction by at least 600%
- · Handled email marketing with Mail Chimp.



EDUCATION

Emory University

BA in Film and Media, 2021

- Maintained a 3.6 GPA
- Consistent dean's lister
- Features editor of the college newspaper